Dillon Nethercote

Student

I'm a third-year university student studying a Bachelor of Information Technology at Griffith University. My passion for learning and growing as a person has encouraged me to find experience in the industry whilst still studying. I'm interested in networking and security with hobbies including full stack web development and software engineering. So far in my degree I have learnt the importance of ITIL best practices, information systems analysis and design, how software languages operate and most importantly customer facing skills. version 2.4

Education

2019-01 **Griffith University, Brisbane**

- present Bachelor of Information Technology, Networks and Security

- 2016-11 St. Mary's College, Maryborough

High School

Awards

Griffith Award for Academic Excellence

Awarded for achieving a GPA of 6.0 or greater in 2020

Griffith Futures Scholarship - 2020

Work History

2019-09

- present

Bottle Shop Assistant

BWS. Brisbane

Current casual employee for BWS. A focus in customer service and support, de-escalation of intense situations and customer safety.

 Responsible for the service of alcohol and tobacco with strong interpersonal and communications skills

2018-09

Cashier/Cook

- 2019-09

Grill'd, Brisbane

A back-area cook focusing on delivering quality meals to customers.

• Responsible for food safety procedures, quality assurance and time management

2017-01

Team Leader

- 2018-08

Macdonald's, Brisbane

Team Leader at Macdonald's responsible for team performance and managing others

2015-01

Customer Service Team Member

- 2016-12

Big W, Maryborough

A part-time employee at Big W working for the customer service team.

· Responsible for customer support and quality service, both in-store and over the phone

Personal Info

Email

dillon.nethercote@gmail.com

Phone

0427201658

Address

Brisbane, Australia

LinkedIn

www.linkedin.com/in/dillon-nethercote

Skills

Communication

Teamwork

Time management

Problem solving

Positive attitude

Microsoft office



Software

*** Html *** Css **** Phpmyadmin Mysql ****